{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Roof Coating \u0026 Sealing Contractors","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40393/":{"taskOID":40393,"originalTaskOID":40393,"setID":687,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5064,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Sealant","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose for the roof sealant treatment? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":852,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"As regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"As regular maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6397,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"To extend the life of the roof","answerDisplayText":"To extend the life of the roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6413,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"To repair leak(s)","answerDisplayText":"To repair leak(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6411,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To prevent leaks","answerDisplayText":"To prevent leaks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6401,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"To improve the roof's appearance","answerDisplayText":"To improve the roof's appearance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4981,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Putting home on the market","answerDisplayText":"Putting home on the market","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5067,"questionDisplayText":"Stories of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5064,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Sealant","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose for the roof sealant treatment? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":852,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"As regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"As regular maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6397,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"To extend the life of the roof","answerDisplayText":"To extend the life of the roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6413,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"To repair leak(s)","answerDisplayText":"To repair leak(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6411,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To prevent leaks","answerDisplayText":"To prevent leaks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6401,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"To improve the roof's appearance","answerDisplayText":"To improve the roof's appearance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4981,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Putting home on the market","answerDisplayText":"Putting home on the market","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":852,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"As regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"As regular maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6397,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"To extend the life of the roof","answerDisplayText":"To extend the life of the roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6413,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"To repair leak(s)","answerDisplayText":"To repair leak(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6411,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To prevent leaks","answerDisplayText":"To prevent leaks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6401,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"To improve the roof's appearance","answerDisplayText":"To improve the roof's appearance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4981,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Putting home on the market","answerDisplayText":"Putting home on the market","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5067,"questionDisplayText":"Stories of Home","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6339,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376527473pwspr007F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40393/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40393,"taskName":"Sealant for Roof - Apply","taskDescription":"Apply Roof Sealant","xmTaskDescriptor":"Roof Coating \u0026 Sealing Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":200,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Roofers Apply prosource prescreened national","textMessagingName":"Roof Sealant","rolloverLongDesc":"Used to extend the life of asphalt, tile \u0026 shake shingle roofs by sealing cracks \u0026 joints \u0026 preventing water penetration.","rolloverShortDesc":"Applying chemicals that seal a roof \u0026 extend its life.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Apply Roof Sealant.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Roof Coating \u0026 Sealing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Apply Roof Coat \u0026 Sealant","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Roof Sealant Application","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Sealant for Roof - Apply","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Roof Sealant Project","urlName":"Sealant-for-Roof-Apply","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Roof Coating \u0026 Sealing Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Roofers,Apply,prosource,prescreened,national,local,roofs,exterior,build,conctractors,roofers.com,wanted,designs,coating,bids,,seal,rooofing,siding,,Roof,exchange,Roofing,License,Sealant","emcCategoryOid":-12061,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":687,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}